Guide to the Sisterhood is Global Institute Records, 1963-2010 and undated, bulk 1980-2002 RL.01185
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Project Files Series, 1990-2003 and undated, 13 boxes
  The series is arranged in two subseries, HRE (Human Rights Education), a major SIGI program, and Other Projects, both of which are further divided into groups. The series contains correspondence with field coordinators, financial records, narrative reports with detailed descriptions of workshop sessions, evaluations, photographs from sessions and meetings, as well as newspaper articles reporting on SIGI's projects in different countries. Material pertaining to SIGI/Jordan, an affiliate center in Amman established to provide computer training and resources on women's rights, can be found in the groups of folders related to Jordan in both subsersies. A large number of workshop evaluations and some of the newspaper clippings are in Arabic. The bulk of the series is organized by geographic location, then by name of SIGI coordinator or project partner.
  - HRE Subseries, 1990s-2001 and undated
    The HRE Subseries contains primarily administrative materials (correspondence, contracts and other financial documents, reports, and evaluations) from the late 1990s that pertain to SIGI’s major core program, the Human Rights Education Project, a series of 12 workshops aimed at empowering women in Muslim societies to define and reclaim their human rights. Countries most frequently represented in the subseries include Azerbaijan, Bangladesh, Pakistan, Syria, and Uzbekistan. There is also extensive material from Jordan and Lebanon, where the HRE Project, in cooperation with the Learning and Partnership Project, incorporated computer and office training. Materials from Jordan and Lebanon are accompanied by a large number of photographs. Finally, there are documents related to SIGI’s HRE radio projects. (Please note that eight audiocassettes originally located together with HRE ratio projects materials can now be found in the Audiovisual Materials Series.)
    The subseries is organized alphabetically by country or region; materials within each group are in original alphabetical order. At the end of each country/region group, there are materials related to the more recent extension of the HRE Project, Expanding HRE, as well as HRE Reports that were originally filed together.
    - Algeria (Box PF1)
      - Expanding HRE
        - Institut Francais d'Archeologie Orientale, 1996 (Box PF1)
        - Meridian International, 1997-1999 and undated (Box PF1)
    - Azerbaijan
      - Expanding HRE, 1997-1999 (Box PF1)
      - Khazar University, 1997-1998 (Box PF1)
      - Nassirova, Firangiz
        - Correspondence, 1997-1999, 2 folders (Box PF1)
        - Finances and contract, 1997-1999 (Box PF1)
        - Resume, 1997 (Box PF1)
      - Reports, 2000-2001 (Box PF1)
      - Workshop materials, undated (Box PF1)
    - Bangladesh
      - Expanding HRE
        - Contacts, 1997 and undated (Box PF1)
      - Finance, 1996-1999 (Box PF1)
      - Report, 2000 (Box PF1)
      - Shefali, Mashuda
        - Correspondence, 1997-1999, 2 folders (Box PF1)
    - Bosnia-Herzegovina
      - Expanding HRE, 1999 (Box PF1)
    - Congo
      - Expanding HRE, 1999 (Box PF1)
    - Egypt
      - Tadros Marlyn
        - Correspondence, 1997-1999, 2 folders (Box PF1)
        - Finances and contracts, 1998-1999 (Box PF1)
    - Egypt (Box PF2)
      - Expanding HRE, 1999 (Box PF2)
      - Reports, 2000 (Box PF2)
    - General
      - Expanding HRE
        - New Model, undated (Box PF2)
        - UNESCO, 1997 (Box PF2)
        - UN Refugee Agency, 1997 (Box PF2)
    - India
      - Expanding HRE
        - Contacts, 1997 (Box PF2)
      - Kazi, Seema
        - Correspondence, 1997-1999, (2 folders) (Box PF2)
        - Finance, 1998-1999 (Box PF2)
      - Reports, 1998-2000 (Box PF2)
    - Ghana
      - Expanding HRE
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1998 (Box PF2)
    - Jordan
      - Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box PF2)
      - Finance, 1997-1998 (Box PF2)
      - Funding proposals, 1998-1999 (Box PF2)
      - Khader, Asma
        - Correspondence, 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box PF2)
    - Jordan (Box PF3)
      - People's Rights: Newspaper of legal research and resource center, 1996-1997 (Box PF3)
      - Reports, 1997-2000, 2 folders (Box PF3)
      - Workshop evaluations, 1998 Oct. 4 (Box PF3)
    - Kazakhstan
      - Expanding HRE, 1997-1998 (Box PF3)
    - Kyrgyzstan
      - Expanding HRE, 1997-1998 (Box PF3)
    - Latin America
      - Expanding HRE
        - Guadalupe Lopez Tov, 1998 (Box PF3)
        - Thais Corral, 1998 (Box PF3)
        - WOLA (Washington Office on Latin America), 1997 and undated (Box PF3)
    - Lebanon
      - Arsanios, Afifa Dirani
        - Correspondence, 1997-1999, 2 folders (Box PF3)
        - Finance, 1996-1999 (Box PF3)
        - Reports, 1997 (Box PF3)
      - Evaluations, 1998 Sept. (Box PF3)
      - Human rights and legal literacy, 1995 June 9-10 (Box PF3)
      - Report regarding partnership program, 2000 (Box PF3)
      - UNIFEM, 1997 (Box PF3)
    - Malaysia
      - Anwar, Zainah
        - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box PF3)
        - Finances and contract, 1998 (Box PF3)
        - Reports, 1998 (Box PF3)
    - Malaysia (Box PF4)
      - Tahir Sharifah
        - Background, 1995-1999 and undated (Box PF4)
    - Mexico
      - Expanding HRE
        - Marcos, Sylvia, 1998 and undated (Box PF4)
    - Middle East
      - Expanding HRE, 1999 (Box PF4)
    - Morocco
      - Expanding HRE
        - Amnesty International, 1997 (Box PF4)
        - Claiming our Rights, 1998 and undated (Box PF4)
        - Meridian Center, 1999 (Box PF4)
        - Moroccan women, 1997 (Box PF4)
        - Other organizations, 1999 (Box PF4)
    - Mosambique
      - Expanding HRE, 1999 (Box PF4)
    - Nigeria
      - Expanding HRE
        - Center for Responsive Politics, 1999 (Box PF4)
    - Pakistan
      - Yacoobi, Sakena
        - Contacts, c.v., organization, 1998 (Box PF4)
        - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box PF4)
        - Finance, 1998 (Box PF4)
        - Reports, 1999-2000 (Box PF4)
      - Expanding HRE
        - Contacts, 1999 (Box PF4)
    - Palestine
      - Expanding HRE
        - Amnesty, 1999 (Box PF4)
        - Azzouni, Suheir, 1997-1998 (Box PF4)
    - Radio Projects
      - Julian Hollic's project, 1997-1999 (Box PF4)
      - Sarina Khan materials, 1998-1999 (Box PF4)
      - Thais Corral, 1999 (Box PF4)
    - Russia
      - Expanding HRE
        - Contacts, 1998 (Box PF4)
        - Human Rights Watch, 1995-1997 (Box PF4)
        - International Humanitarian Fund, 1999 and undated (Box PF4)
        - Marina Pisklakova, 1998 (Box PF4)
        - Russian lawyers, 1998 (Box PF4)
    - South Africa
      - Expanding HRE
        - Tandaswa Ndita, undated (Box PF4)
        - Tshawarang Legal Advocacy Center, 1998 (Box PF4)
    - Syria (Box PF5)
      - Shaaban, Bouthaina
        - Correspondence, 1997-1999, 2 folders (Box PF5)
        - Evaluations, in Arabic 1998 Oct. 4 (Box PF5)
        - Finances and contract, 1997-1999 (Box PF5)
        - Reports, 1998 and undated (Box PF5)
      - Report, 2000-2001 (Box PF5)
    - Tajikistan
      - NGOs, 1998-1999 and undated (Box PF5)
    - Tunisia
      - Expanding HRE, 1999 (Box PF5)
    - Turkey
      - Expanding HRE
        - Senal Sarihan, 1996-1997 (Box PF5)
    - Turkmenistan
      - Information Folder, 1999 (Box PF5)
    - Uzbekistan
      - Contacts, 1999 and undated (Box PF5)
      - Contracts, 2000 (Box PF5)
      - Flora Pirznarova, 1998 (Box PF5)
      - Initial stages for setup, 1990s (Box PF5)
      - Reports, 1997, 2 folders (Box PF5)
    - Uzbekistan (Box PF6)
      - Reports, 1998, 2000, 3 folders (Box PF6)
      - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua
        - Correspondence, 1997-1999, 4 folders (Box PF6)
        - Finances, 1997-1998 (Box PF6)
        - Reports, 1999 and undated (Box PF6)
  - Other Projects Subseries, 1990-2003 and undated
    The Other Projects Subseries is divided into six groups. The Country Projects group consists of administrative materials that relate to the continuation of the HRE Project in various countries, as well as documents pertaining to new programs, including the KPP (Knowledge Partnership Program) and Building Local Leaders Initiative. SIGI members project coordinators and partners. The subseries also contains some administrative materials related to SIGI’s proposed projects and potential partners. Other folders contain SIGI alerts on violations of women's human rights which have been issued between the years 1990 and 2003. Some reports and correspondence are available for another major SIGI program, Violence against Women (VAW). Finally, there are materials on SIGI’s research project on the effect of the demise of fisheries on the women who work in them in five key areas of the world. This last group of materials also includes notes and the final essay, Of Fish and Women by Lise Moisan. All materials in the Other Projects Subseries are in original alphabetical order, with the exception of the Alerts, which are organized chronologically.
    - Alerts (Box PF7)
      - SIGI Alerts
        - 1990
          - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec. (Box PF7)
        - 1991
          - Miscellaneous, July-Sept. (Box PF7)
          - Aminita Diop, Mali, Nov. (Box PF7)
        - 1992
          - Aung Son Suu Kyi, Burma, Jan. (Box PF7)
          - Wangari Maathai, Kenya, Jan. (Box PF7)
          - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec. (Box PF7)
          - Ireland Abortion Alert, Feb. (Box PF7)
          - Comfort Camps, Bosnia, Aug.-Oct. (Box PF7)
          - Soheila Aeinechi, Nov. (Box PF7)
        - 1993
          - Miscellaneous, Feb.-Sept. (Box PF7)
          - AWSA, Egypt, June (Box PF7)
          - Bosnia Rape Alert, Sept. (Box PF7)
          - Asylum Alert, Dec. (Box PF7)
          - Rabiha Shtieya, Dec. (Box PF7)
        - 1994
          - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Nov. (Box PF7)
          - Homa Darabu, Mar. (Box PF7)
          - Algerian Women Alert, May (Box PF7)
          - Haitian Women Alert, July (Box PF7)
        - 1995
          - Rwanda, Jan. (Box PF7)
          - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec. (Box PF7)
          - Beijing, Apr. (Box PF7)
          - Bangladesh, May (Box PF7)
          - US Foreign Aid, May (Box PF7)
          - Saba Abd-Ali and Zeynab Hiydari, July (Box PF7)
        - 1996
          - Cedaw Optional Protocol, Jan. (Box PF7)
          - Miscellaneous, Jan.-Oct. (Box PF7)
          - Equal Pay, Japan, Mar. (Box PF7)
          - Kalpana Chakma, Bangladesh, July (Box PF7)
    - Alerts (Box PF8)
      - SIGI Alerts
        - 1996
          - Egypt, Aug. (Box PF8)
          - Mexico, Aug. (Box PF8)
          - Afghanistan, Sept. (Box PF8)
        - 1997
          - Other, Jan.-Dec. (Box PF8)
          - Family Planning Alert, Feb. 14 (Box PF8)
          - ICC (International Criminal Court), Feb. 20 (Box PF8)
          - Nigeria, Mar. 27 (Box PF8)
          - Female Genital Mutilation Alert, July 11 (Box PF8)
          - Nepal, Aug. 15 (Box PF8)
          - Sudan, Dec. (Box PF8)
        - 1998
          - Other, Jan.-Apr. (Box PF8)
          - Iran, Apr. 24 (Box PF8)
          - Iran 2, May 28 (Box PF8)
          - Rape Definition Alert, Sept. (Box PF8)
        - 1999
          - Wangari Maathai Attack, Jan. 19 (Box PF8)
          - Prostitution, Feb. (Box PF8)
          - Acid Attacks, Bangladesh, Mar. 17 (Box PF8)
          - Iran, Apr. 12 (Box PF8)
          - Rosemary Nelso, Apr. 20 (Box PF8)
          - Pakistan, Apr. (Box PF8)
          - Possible Alerts, May-Sept. (Box PF8)
          - Zimbabwe, June (Box PF8)
    - Alerts (Box PF9)
      - SIGI Alerts
        - 1999
          - Pakistan 2, Aug. 31 (Box PF9)
          - Kuwait, Nov. 24 (Box PF9)
        - 2000
          - Nizkor (Spanish translation), Jan. (Box PF9)
          - Nunavut, Jan.-Dec. (Box PF9)
          - Austria, Feb. (Box PF9)
          - Responses to Austria, Feb. (Box PF9)
          - Prostitution, Sept. (Box PF9)
          - World March of Women, Sept. (Box PF9)
        - 2001
          - Nigeria, Jan. 5 (Box PF9)
          - Global proliferation of small arms and weapons, Mar. (Box PF9)
          - Nawal El Saadawi, May (Box PF9)
          - Follow-up on Hesba, May-Aug. (Box PF9)
          - Afghan Women's Summit, Dec. 4-6 (Box PF9)
        - 2003
          - Nigeria and Iran Stonings, Jan. (Box PF9)
          - Responses to Nigeria and Iran Stonings, Feb. (Box PF9)
      - Non-SIGI Alerts
        - 1993-1996
          - Equality Now (Box PF9)
          - Other (Box PF9)
        - 1994-1997
          - Women Living Under Muslim Law (Box PF9)
    - Alerts (Box PF10)
      - Non-SIGI Alerts
        - 2001
          - Women’s Economic Rights Alerts, by Women’s Rights Watch, Nigeria (Box PF10)
        - 2001-2002
          - Middle East reports, vigils (Box PF10)
          - Stonings, violence against women alerts, from Women’s Rights Watch, Nigeria, 2 folders (Box PF10)
        - 2002-2003
          - Stonings, floggings, and other VAWs (Box PF10)
    - Country Projects
      - Afghanistan
        - Articles and information sites, 2001-2003 (Box PF10)
        - Distance Education
          - University of Ottawa, 2001 (Box PF10)
          - Yacoobi, Sakena, 2000 (Box PF10)
        - Initiatives and campaign involvements by SIGI, 2001 (Box PF10)
        - International campaigns, 2001-2002 (Box PF10)
        - KPP (Knowledge Partnership Program), 2000-2001 (Box PF10)
        - Partnership with RefWID (Refugee Women in Development), 2002 (Box PF10)
        - Pershawar Project proposal, 2000 and undated (Box PF10)
        - Summit for Democracy, 2001-2002 (Box PF10)
        - Women for Women, Montreal chapter (Box PF10)
      - Azerbaijan
        - Nassirova, Firangiz
          - Background, 1999 (Box PF10)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999-2000 (Box PF10)
          - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box PF10)
          - Reports, 1999 (Box PF10)
      - Bangladesh
        - Gems of Hope, 1998-1999 and undated (Box PF10)
        - Microcredit, 2000 (Box PF10)
    - Country Projects (Box PF11)
      - Bangladesh
        - Shefali, Mashuda Khatun
          - Background, 1997-1999 and undated (Box PF11)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF11)
          - Correspondence, 1999 (Box PF11)
      - Egypt
        - Tadros, Marlyn
          - Background, 1998-1999 (Box PF11)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF11)
          - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box PF11)
          - Reports, 1998-1999 (Box PF11)
      - India
        - Kazi, Seema
          - Background, 1998-1999 (Box PF11)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF11)
          - Correspondence, 1999 (Box PF11)
          - Reports, 1998-1999 (Box PF11)
      - Israel
        - Building Local Leaders Initiatives, undated (Box PF11)
        - Correspondence, 2001 (Box PF11)
        - Freedman, Marcia, 2000-2001 (Box PF11)
        - Information for Mizrachi Harduf, 2000 (Box PF11)
        - Ester Meir, 2000 (Box PF11)
        - Physicians for Human Rights, 1999 (Box PF11)
      - Jordan
        - Brochures, posters, and photos, 1999 and undated (Box PF11)
        - Khader, Asma
          - Background, 1999 and undated (Box PF11)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF11)
          - Correspondence, 1999 (Box PF11)
          - KPP, 1999 (Box PF11)
          - Reports, 1999, 2 folders (Box PF11)
        - KPP reports, 1999-2000 (Box PF11)
        - Workshop reports, 1999 (Box PF11)
    - Country Projects (Box PF12)
      - Lebanon
        - Arsanios, Afifa Dirani
          - Background, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Correspondence, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - KPP reports, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Reports, 1998-1999 (Box PF12)
        - KPP reports, 1999-2000 (Box PF12)
      - Pakistan
        - KPP reports, 1999-2000 (Box PF12)
        - Yacoobi, Sakena
          - Background, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Correspondence, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Reports, 1999, 2 folders (Box PF12)
      - Syria
        - Minutes from the COR Workshop, 1999-2001 (Box PF12)
        - Shaaban, Bouthaina
          - Background, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Correspondence, 1999 (Box PF12)
          - Reports, 1999 (Box PF12)
    - Country Projects (Box PF13)
      - Uzbekistan
        - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua
          - Background, 1999 (Box PF13)
          - Contracts and finances, 1999 (Box PF13)
          - Correspondence, 1999 (Box PF13)
          - Reports, 1999 (Box PF13)
      - Yemen
        - Workshops, 1998 (Box PF13)
      - Zimbabwe
        - Musasa Project Safe and Secure, 1997-1999 and undated (Box PF13)
        - Rudo Kwaramba correspondence, 1999 (Box PF13)
    - Fisheries
      - Aoua Bocar Ly-Tall, 2000 and undated (Box PF13)
      - Auou Bocar Ly-Tall contracts for preliminary research, 2000 (Box PF13)
      - Bare Bones outline (a position paper on the world's fisheries and women's place in it by Lise Moisan), 1990s-2000s (Box PF13)
      - Contracts with Lise Moisan, 2000 (Box PF13)
      - General information, 2002 and undated (Box PF13)
      - Lise Moisan's CV, undated (Box PF13)
      - Of Fish and Women, 2000 Dec. (Box PF13)
      - Overview for Women and Fisheries Project, 2000 and undated (Box PF13)
      - Preliminary fisheries report by Aoua Bocar Ly-Tall, 2000 June (Box PF13)
    - Potential Partnership
      - Dalit Nepal, 1995-2000 and undated (Box PF13)
      - Empowering Afghan Women's NGOs, partnership with RefWID, 2000 and undated (Box PF13)
      - FEDO (Feminist Dalit Organization), 2000 (Box PF13)
      - General, 1997 (Box PF13)
      - HRE/VAW Building Local Leaders Initiative, undated (Box PF13)
      - Indonesia, 2000
        - Correspondence (Box PF13)
        - Report from Jacarta (Box PF13)
      - Morocco, 1999 (Box PF13)
      - Requests for projects with SIGI, 2000-2001 (Box PF13)
      - Tobique, 2001 (Box PF13)
    - Proposals
      - Canadian one pagers, undated (Box PF13)
      - General support one pager, undated (Box PF13)
      - Israel one pagers, undated (Box PF13)
      - Long document about SIGI history and capacity, undated (Box PF13)
      - Short SIGI history and capacity, undated (Box PF13)
    - VAW
      - Egypt-Marlyn Tadros, 1998 (Box PF13)
      - Jordan, 1998 and undated (Box PF13)
      - Lebanon-Afifa correspondence, 1998-1999 and undated (Box PF13)
      - Lebanon-Afifa regarding Farida Benhami, 1998 (Box PF13)
      - Zimbabwe-Rudo Kwaramba, 1998-1999 (Box PF13)
- Publications Series, 1981-2003 and undated, bulk 1993-2001, 18 boxes
  Contains administrative records most of SIGI publications, chiefly copyright documentation and distribution lists, as well as drafts, translations, and published versions for each individual publication. Also included are translation contracts and occasional correspondence with editors and translators. SIGI manual, Claiming Our Rights, with its translations, constitutes the largest group in the series. Numerous drafts and translations are also available for In Our Own Words and Safe and Secure. The series contains 14 issues and the edited proofs of SIGI News. Records related to Muslim Women and the Politics of Participation, Sisterhood Is Global Book, and Strategizing on Safety are sparse. No materials related to Faith and Freedom: Women's Human Rights in the Muslim World are available in the series.
  Organized alphabetically by subject and publication, then alphabetically within, except for SIGI News, which is organized chronologically by year and issue. A large amount of documents are translations into Arabic, Azeri, Bangla, French, Hindi, Malay, Persian (Farsi), Russian, Urdu, and Uzbek. (Electronic disks 014-056, mostly translations and drafts, have been removed from the series.)
  - Administrative (Box PUB1)
    - Book exchange, comments on Claming Our Rights, 1998-1999 (Box PUB1)
    - Book lists for Claiming Our Rights and others, 1999 (Box PUB1)
    - Books donated
      - 2000, 2003 (Box PUB1)
      - Donated to charities or exchanged with other groups, 2001 Feb. (Box PUB1)
    - Books given to NGOs, charities, or for project initiation, 2000 (Box PUB1)
    - Books in print
      - Bowker Data Collection, 2000 (Box PUB1)
      - Bowker database transactions, 2001 (Box PUB1)
      - Bowker Link, registration updates for 2001, 2001 June (Box PUB1)
      - Canada, undated (Box PUB1)
    - Books to be invoiced, 2000 Aug. 8 (Box PUB1)
    - Copyright
      - Canada, 2001 May (Box PUB1)
      - Claiming Our Rights
        - 1998 Dec. (Box PUB1)
        - Arabic, 1999 Apr. 16 (Box PUB1)
        - Azeri, Bangla, 1999 July 26 (Box PUB1)
        - Bangla, 2000 Jan. 3 (Box PUB1)
        - Hindi, 1999 Aug. 2 (Box PUB1)
        - Malay, 1999 Aug. 2 (Box PUB1)
        - Persian, 1999 Aug. 2 (Box PUB1)
        - Urdu, 2000 Jan. 3 (Box PUB1)
        - Uzbek, 1999 Aug. 2 (Box PUB1)
      - Permission requests to SIGI
        - For Safe and Secure, 2000 June 26 (Box PUB1)
        - For SIGI's Urgent Action Alert, 2000 Sept. (Box PUB1)
      - Safe and Secure, 1998 Dec. (Box PUB1)
      - Strategizing for Safety, 2000 Jan. 3 (Box PUB1)
      - Supplementary registration, 2000 Aug. (Box PUB1)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box PUB1)
    - Invoices paid, 1999, 3 folders (Box PUB1)
    - ISBN
      - 1998-1999 (Box PUB1)
      - Canada, 2001 (Box PUB1)
    - Letter and questionnaire for book exchange/donation, undated (Box PUB1)
    - Letters of accompaniment for manual sent out for new translations, 2001 May (Box PUB1)
    - List of organizations receiving Safe and Secure in exchange for publications, correspondence, 1999, 2 folders (Box PUB1)
    - List of people receiving a free copy of Safe and Secure, correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box PUB1)
    - List of people receiving In Our Own Words, 1999 (Box PUB1)
    - List of SIGI publications, undated (Box PUB1)
    - Manuals, Abco printing, quotes, number of copies, 2001 (Box PUB1)
  - Administrative (Box PUB2)
    - National Library of Canada, legal deposits and forms, 2001, 2 folders (Box PUB2)
    - National Library of Quebec, legal deposits and forms in French, 2001, 2 folders (Box PUB2)
    - SIGI publications order form, undated (Box PUB2)
  - Claiming Our Rights
    - Arabic
      - 1999, 6 folders (Box PUB2)
      - Abderrahim Sahir's edits, 1999 Jan. 26 (Box PUB2)
      - Correspondence
        - Human rights education, 1996-1999 (Box PUB2)
        - With Abderrahim Sahir, 1998-1999 (Box PUB2)
      - Preliminary adaptation, 1999 (Box PUB2)
  - Claiming Our Rights (Box PUB3)
    - Arabic
      - Translation of second edition
        - 1999 Jan. 19 (Box PUB3)
        - Corrections, Marlyn Tadros, 1999 (Box PUB3)
        - Khader, Asma, 1999 (Box PUB3)
        - Khatib, Mohammad, 1999 (Box PUB3)
      - Translation of sessions 9-12, Khader, Asma, 2001 Nov. (Box PUB3)
    - Azeri
      - 1999, 3 folders (Box PUB3)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1998-1999 (Box PUB3)
        - With Hassan Javadi, 1998 Nov. 19 (Box PUB3)
      - Final draft, 1999 July (Box PUB3)
  - Claiming Our Rights (Box PUB4)
    - Azeri
      - Horowitz, Dilshad, 1999 June 1, 2 folders (Box PUB4)
      - Nassirova, Firanqiz, 1996, 1998, 2 folders (Box PUB4)
      - Samples, 1998-1999 (Box PUB4)
    - Bangla
      - Correction of title, third edition, 1997-1998 (Box PUB4)
      - Corrections, Dasgupta, Indrani, 1998 Oct. 9 (Box PUB4)
      - Correspondence
        - Hashemi, Syed, 1999 (Box PUB4)
        - Huq, Shireen, 1997-1998 (Box PUB4)
        - Jahan, Roushan, 1998 (Box PUB4)
  - Claiming Our Rights (Box PUB5)
    - Bangla
      - Hashemi, Syed, 1999 July 10 (Box PUB5)
      - Preliminary adaptation, 1999 and undated, 4 folders (Box PUB5)